(Leonard:)- You hold this.
- Whoa, that's heavy.
- Oh, you don't have on any jewelry, do you?
- No, why?
(Leonard:)Grad student forgot to take out
one of his piercings.
(Leonard:)Now he's on a transplant list
waiting for a nipple his size.
(Leonard:)Now, watch this.
(Penny:)Whoa.
(Penny:)That is very cool.
(Leonard:)Sometimes I like to turn this on
and pretend I'm the super-villain Magneto.
(Penny:)Getting a little less cool, Leonard.
(Leonard:)What I really am is a very smart scientist.
(Leonard:)Who understands
the mechanics of the universe.
(Leonard:)And is wearing the sexy black
underwear you bought.
- There we go.
- Yeah.
(Raj:)So I thought the photo booth for the party
could be creepy, like a mummy's tomb...
(Raj:)...or they also have
the TARDIS from Doctor Who.
(Sheldon:)A TARDIS makes no sense.
(Sheldon:)A time machine from a science-fiction show
has nothing to do with Halloween.